medreporters24.com 2018-08-14

# MedicReporter - medical information portal devoted to health

The privacy of Internet users visiting our website is extremely important. The following information was posted into the personal data that is stored at registration. We emphasize that we do not pass this data to any other entities and do not share them for commercial purposes.

**Confidentiality of personal data**

All personal data are archived upon the consent of the user and are used exclusively by the Publisher of the Portal. Personal data are needed to identify Internet users visiting the Portal. Only such information as: the user name and email address. Personal information is not shared with any external entities. All visitors to the portal shall have the rights as set out in the Act on Protection of Personal Data.

**Cooperation with Google**

This Portal uses Google Analytics – a service of monitoring web page views provided by Google Inc. In this process, Google Analytics uses "cookies" - files that allow a site to track the way of using the site by the user. Google Inc. may provide this information to third parties only when required by legal provisions.

**"Cookies”**

We use "cookies" to collect information about your individual preferences and interests arising from using the Portal. These files store personal browser settings and prompts given in the automatic refilling of form fields.

**Questions about the privacy policy**

If you have any doubts, please contact us. We will answer all your questions regarding the privacy policy on our website. You can ask questions via the "Contact" tab.

Using the Portal constitutes acceptance of the principles described above.
